

# **BENJAMIN SOLT**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Engineer who is eager to grow and learn new programs.

Prior experience includes 10 years in retail, developing skills in teamwork, communication, and customer service.

Have Bachelors of Science. In addition took initiative, self taught Epic Games, Unreal Engine.

#### **SKILLS**

- CSS
- HTML
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Unreal Engine
- 3D Studio Max
- Python
- neact Tythic

#### **EDUCATION**

### LAMBDA SCHOOL - REMOTE

July 2019 - Present Full Stack Web Developer

## TEMPLE UNIVERSITY CERTIFICATION IN WEBSITE DESIGN

May 2012

- Intensive course focused on creative web design
- page layouts and art assets
- Utilized HTML, CSS and Dreamweaver

#### THE ART INSTITUTE OF PHILADELPHIA

December 2007

 Bachelor of Science Degree in Media Arts and Animation

#### **CONTACT INFO**

- Bensolt@gmail.com
- Cell: 215 360 5410
- Fort Washington, PA
- Bensolt.com
- <u>LinkedIn</u>
- Github

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **PORTFOLIO**

April 2020 - Present Built to showcase personal projects. HTML/CSS | JavaScript | React

#### GROA

Feb 17 2020, 8 weeks

Built to recommend movies to user, based on how user rates movies HTML/CSS | JavaScript | React | AWS

- As Front End Developer built Authorization, Login, display layout of movie info
- Solved problems and trouble shot bugs with team members
- Collaborated remotely with team of 6 web developers, 2 data science, and 1 UX designer

#### **REACT-REDUX-APP2**

December 2019

Built to demonstrate API call and Redux. HTML/CSS | JavaScript | React? | Halo API

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **FRESH MARKET**

HORSHAM, PA

AUGUST 2016 - JUNE 2019

#### **GIANT GROCERY STORE**

WILLOW GROVE, PA

NOVEMBER 2013 - AUGUST 2016

- Produce Associate
- Restock produce and ensure available products are fresh daily
- Respond to shopper inquiries, assist with locating specific products and provide overall friendly customer service